<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homeopathica</title>
    <link>https://homepathica.ca/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Homeopathica</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>vzhmurko@gmail.com (Veronika Zhmurko)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>vzhmurko@gmail.com (Veronika Zhmurko)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 04:51:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://homepathica.ca/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>legal</title>
      <link>https://homepathica.ca/legal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 04:51:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>vzhmurko@gmail.com (Veronika Zhmurko)</author>
      <guid>https://homepathica.ca/legal/</guid>
      <description>This website is for educational and informational purposes only and should not be used for diagnosis or medical treatment or relied on as an alternative to conventional medical advice from a qualified and licensed medical practitioner or healthcare professional. By using this website you agree to be bound by the terms of use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Credentials</title>
      <link>https://homepathica.ca/credentials/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 04:35:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>vzhmurko@gmail.com (Veronika Zhmurko)</author>
      <guid>https://homepathica.ca/credentials/</guid>
      <description>Medical Credentials Veronika has a traditional European Medical Education. As such, she underwent all the training that medical doctors in North America receive and more. Her extra studies included courses in preventative medicine (e.g. hygiene), nature-based treatments (including herbology, hydrotherapy and oxygen therapy), and homeopathy. Ultimately, she would go on to earn a doctorate in clinical immunology.
After graduation from medical school, Veronika worked in the Ukraine as a family doctor and general practitioner for 10 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Homeopathy</title>
      <link>https://homepathica.ca/about-homeopathy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 04:25:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>vzhmurko@gmail.com (Veronika Zhmurko)</author>
      <guid>https://homepathica.ca/about-homeopathy/</guid>
      <description>German Science Homeopathy is a science-based system of medicine based on the discoveries and observations of 19th century German physician and chemist, Samuel Hahnemann. This safe and effective treatment method uses the principle of &amp;lsquo;similars,&amp;rsquo; or &amp;lsquo;like cures like,&amp;rsquo; from which its name is derived. As such, Hahnemann cured illness using the smallest possible doses of a medicinal substance that creates similar symptoms in a healthy individual.
Single Simple Remedy From that day to this, classical homeopaths have used the Law of Similars, and the principal of the minimum possible dose, to diagnose and treat their patients: either human or animal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lifestyle</title>
      <link>https://homepathica.ca/post/lifestyle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 04:23:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>vzhmurko@gmail.com (Veronika Zhmurko)</author>
      <guid>https://homepathica.ca/post/lifestyle/</guid>
      <description>Lifestyle Advice Chronic illness leads to acidification of the body. A good diet helps alkalize tissues, and thus improves overall health. The best alkalizing method includes drinking fresh lemon or lime juice, or a rosehip infusion. Juice from half a lemon or lime should be squeezed, and the juice should be added to a glass of mineral water.
Physical exercise is absolutely essential for the proper absorption of nutrients. “The diet without physical activity cannot keep people healthy,” said Hippocrates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>eating</title>
      <link>https://homepathica.ca/post/eating/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 04:18:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>vzhmurko@gmail.com (Veronika Zhmurko)</author>
      <guid>https://homepathica.ca/post/eating/</guid>
      <description>Appetite and Eating Habits The only time that you should be eating is when you are hungry. Trust me, this is actually easier said than done. However it is the first step to healthy eating habits and can be the undoing of many other weight-loss attempts
Keep a regular eating schedule: try to eat every day at the same time and avoid snacking between meals. You should leave the table with a feeling of a slightly empty stomach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>food</title>
      <link>https://homepathica.ca/post/food/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 04:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>vzhmurko@gmail.com (Veronika Zhmurko)</author>
      <guid>https://homepathica.ca/post/food/</guid>
      <description>Food and Dietary Advice Always try to eat the freshest and the least processed food. It is better to use locally grown produce.
Please avoid using a microwave for cooking or even defrosting.
Food should be processed to the least degree while cooking. Baking, broiling, and steaming are excellent choices instead of frying. Oils should be added to the already cooked food.
If occasional eating fried food, it would be recommended to consume some fresh cold pressed oil within the same meal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>contact</title>
      <link>https://homepathica.ca/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>vzhmurko@gmail.com (Veronika Zhmurko)</author>
      <guid>https://homepathica.ca/contact/</guid>
      <description>Veronika Zhmruko MD Ph.D Hom m: 613-401-3835
Thornhill Naturopathic Health Clinic
p: 905-707-2001
Holistic Medical Clinic
2340 Dundas St. West Unit G05, Toronto ON
p: 647 350 6655</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>