<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Homeopathica</title>
    <link>https://sean-stanley.gitlab.io/homeopathica/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Homeopathica</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>vzhmurko@gmail.com (Veronika Zhmurko)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>vzhmurko@gmail.com (Veronika Zhmurko)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 04:23:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sean-stanley.gitlab.io/homeopathica/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>lifestyle</title>
      <link>https://sean-stanley.gitlab.io/homeopathica/post/lifestyle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 04:23:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>vzhmurko@gmail.com (Veronika Zhmurko)</author>
      <guid>https://sean-stanley.gitlab.io/homeopathica/post/lifestyle/</guid>
      <description>Lifestyle Advice Chronic illness leads to acidification of the body. A good diet helps alkalize tissues, and thus improves overall health. The best alkalizing method includes drinking fresh lemon or lime juice, or a rosehip infusion. Juice from half a lemon or lime should be squeezed, and the juice should be added to a glass of mineral water.
Physical exercise is absolutely essential for the proper absorption of nutrients. “The diet without physical activity cannot keep people healthy,” said Hippocrates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>eating</title>
      <link>https://sean-stanley.gitlab.io/homeopathica/post/eating/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 04:18:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>vzhmurko@gmail.com (Veronika Zhmurko)</author>
      <guid>https://sean-stanley.gitlab.io/homeopathica/post/eating/</guid>
      <description>Appetite and Eating Habits The only time that you should be eating is when you are hungry. Trust me, this is actually easier said than done. However it is the first step to healthy eating habits and can be the undoing of many other weight-loss attempts
Keep a regular eating schedule: try to eat every day at the same time and avoid snacking between meals. You should leave the table with a feeling of a slightly empty stomach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>food</title>
      <link>https://sean-stanley.gitlab.io/homeopathica/post/food/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 04:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>vzhmurko@gmail.com (Veronika Zhmurko)</author>
      <guid>https://sean-stanley.gitlab.io/homeopathica/post/food/</guid>
      <description>Food and Dietary Advice Always try to eat the freshest and the least processed food. It is better to use locally grown produce.
Please avoid using a microwave for cooking or even defrosting.
Food should be processed to the least degree while cooking. Baking, broiling, and steaming are excellent choices instead of frying. Oils should be added to the already cooked food.
If occasional eating fried food, it would be recommended to consume some fresh cold pressed oil within the same meal.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>